<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kshitij Agrawal - AI Scientist</title>
    <link>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kshitij Agrawal - AI Scientist</description>
    <image>
      <title>Kshitij Agrawal - AI Scientist</title>
      <url>https://kshitijagrwl.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://kshitijagrwl.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 01:51:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Matting</title>
      <link>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/image-matting-background-removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 01:51:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/image-matting-background-removal/</guid>
      <description>What is Image Matting Natural image matting is a fundamental computer vision task, which aims to predict an alpha matte of the foreground object from a given image. An image can be represented by a linear combination of foreground and background, with a blending of a parameter alpha. Mathematically, image matting is formulated as:
Ii = αiFi + (1 − αi)Bi ,
where Ii, αi, Fi and Bi are observed colour value, alpha value, foreground value and background value of pixel i, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Deep Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/on-metric-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 01:50:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/on-metric-learning/</guid>
      <description>We are witnessing a revival of interest in the space of metric learning or representation learning, due to the popularity of embedding models in the NLP space. I thought of penning down some thoughts on the evolution of metric learning over the years, particularly from the point of view of computer vision.
Learning a powerful and generalizable representation has been of particular interest to researchers, as it has applications across a multitude of tasks like classification, person re-identification, face recognition, information retreival and recommender systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website </title>
      <link>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kshitijagrwl.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few of my areas of interest, general research and things I find interesting.
Areas of Interest - Large Lanuage Models
Sequence classification, topic / doc classification, embeddings, vector search Computer Vision
Semantic Segmentation, Object detection , pose detection Classical image processing Image quality assessment Face Recognition / Face Detection Few Shot Learning , Continual Learning , Metric Learning
Model Deployment &amp;amp; Serving optimization
Here are a list of my publications</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
